Guide to the James A. Baker Institute for Animal Health records, 1915-2003.
Baker, James A. Institute for Animal Health records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
James A. Baker Institute for Animal Health records, 1915-2003.
24-9-3598
James A. Baker Institute for Animal Health.
.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, reports, memorabilia
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Institute News and Views, 1987-1995, Veterinary Virus Research Institute Annual Reports, 1951-1975 and memos and correspondence.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Baker Institute for Animal Health is one of the oldest research centers dedicated to the study of veterinary infectious diseases, immunology, genetics, and reproduction.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Institute News and Views, 1987-1995, Veterinary Virus Research Institute Annual Reports, 1951-1975 and memos and correspondence.
Also, magnet, bookmark, brochure, and notecard, 2009.
Files relating to the history and accomplishments of the Baker Institute and to John M. Olin, including some photographs, 1950-1997.
SUBJECTS
Names:
James A. Baker Institute for Animal Health.; Olin, John M.; Olin, John M.; James A. Baker Institute for Animal Health; James A. Baker Institute for Animal Health.
Subjects:
Veterinary medicine -- Research -- New York (State); Veterinary medicine -- Research
Places:
New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- James Baker Biographical Material, 1915-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- James Baker Publications, Various Dates (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Vet Virus Research Institute Annual Reports, 1951-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Virus Research Institute Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- History of Institute, 1950-2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- John Olin Correspondence, Clippings, 1948-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Institute News and Views, 1987-1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Baker Institute for Animals Health Brochure, no date (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Institute notecards and magnet, 2000s (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Photographs, 1975-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)